Finding Aid for the Lawrence Morton Papers LSC.1522
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research Material
  - Stravinsky, Music By
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concerto (1923-24, revised 1950) for piano and wind instruments., 1960. (Box 40)
      C35(1). Plate no.B. & H. 18766. 8-60 L & B.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--A sermon, a narrative and a prayer (1961). (Box 40)
      S20(1). Plate no.B. & H. 18784. 9-61 L & B.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Eight instrumental miniatures (1962)., 1963.; 3 copies. Two with buff wrappers one with white wrappers. (Box 40)
      I 3(1). Plate no.9906A. DSL lists dedication: Laurence(sic) Morton.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Octet (1923, new version 1952) for wind instruments. (Box 40)
      O 2(1). Plate no.B. & H. 17231. 10-55 L & B. p.1 legend in L.M.'s hand, added for 1952 revision. Changes are marked in pencil throughout.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Chant du rossignol (1917) poeme symphonique pour orchestre., 1921. (Box 40)
      C13(3). Plate no.B. & H. 16312. H.P. B709. 448.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Apollon Musagete (original 1928, rev. 1947) ballet en deux tableaux., 1949. (Box 40)
      A 7(2). Two copies in Box 40. Plate no.B. & H. 16213. 9-62 & 2-49 L & B. On copyright page of 2-49 in L.M.'s hand, Klemperer at premiere 16-14-4-4-6, Stravinsky changed to 8-8-6-4-4-4.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Movements (1959) for piano and orchestra., 1960. (Box 40)
      M13(1). Plate no.B. & H. 18676. 5-60 L & B. Two copies in Box 40, one of which contains occasional serial analysis.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Threni (1958) lamentationes Jeremiae prophetae. (Box 40)
      T 6(1). Plate no.18438. 10-58 & 1-59 L & B. Two copies both with occasional pencil and pen analyses throughout in L.M.'s hand.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Symphonies d'instruments a vent] Symphonies of wind instruments (revised 1947 version)., 1952. (Box 41)
      S40(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Octet (1923--new version 1952) for wind instruments. (Box 41)
      New York: Boosey & Hawkes, Limited.
      O 2(1). p.12 In L.M.'s hand: For repetition of Variation A (3 times in all) cf. Minuet of Mozart Diverimento K. 251, where each of 3 variations is followed by the minuet proper.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concerto en Mi b pour orchestre de chambre (Dumbarton Oaks 8-V-38)., 1938. (Box 41)
      C32(2). This is the first published small score (plate 35383) distinguished from plate 35383a(C32[2a], also in box 41) by the legend 'Printed in England' at the bottom of the cover.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Rag-time (1918) pour onze instruments., 1920.; There are two copies: one clothbound and one in wrappers. (Box 41)
      R 1(3).
    - Stravinsky, Igor'--[Octet] Octuor (1923) pour instruments a vent., 1924.; Clothbound. (Box 41)
      Edited by Albert Spalding.
      Paris: Edition Russe de Musique.
      O 1(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concertino for 12 instruments (1952)., 1953. (Box 41)
      Arrangement of the original work (1920), made by Igor Stravinsky in 1952.
      Copenhagen: Wilhelm Hansen.
      C30(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Jeu de cartes (1936) ballet en 3 donnes., 1937. (Box 41)
      C11(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--L'Histoire du soldat (1918)., 1924. (Box 41)
      Text by C.F. Ramuz.
      H 1(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Symphonie en ut (1940)., 1948. (Box 41)
      S43(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Ode (1943), elegiacal chant in three parts., 1947. (Box 41)
      London: Schott and Company.
      O 4(3).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Les Noces (orchestrated 1923). (Box 41)
      N 1(3?). The plate no. matches, however DSL N 1(3) is listed as full score. This is a small score.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Baiser de la fee] The fairy's kiss (Revised 1950 version)., 1952. (Box 41)
      B 5(2). B. & H. 1669. 1-53 L & B.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concertino pour quatuor a cordes (1920)., 1951. (Box 41)
      Edited and revised by Julia A. Burt, New York.
      Copenhagen: Wilhelm Hansen, Musik-Forlag.
      C28(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Gorodetzky songs opus 6 (1908)., 1912 or 1913. (Box 41)
      Russian text.
      Moscow: Jurgenson Edition (plates 33364 & 33365).
      M11(1). One photocopy and one photographic print in envelope.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Capriccio for piano and orchestra (revised 1949 version)., 1952. (Box 41)
      London: Hawkes & Son, Limited.
      C 9(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Monumentum (1960) pro Gesualdo di Venosa ad CD annum. Three madrigals re-composed for instruments. (Box 41)
      M12(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--L'Histoire du soldat (1918)., n.d. (Box 41)
      New York: Edwin F. Kalmus.
      H 1(3).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Suite [no.2] for small orchestra (1921)., 1926. (Box 41)
      S31(3). From 1925 Chester Edition. Date of composition is incorrectly listed as 1925 in DSL.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Renard (1916)., 1917. (Box 41)
      R 7(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Le Faune et la bergere opus 2 (1906)., 1964, 1913. (Box 41)
      Bonn: M.P. Belaieff.
      F 2(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Quatre etudes pour orchestre (1928)., 1947. (Box 41)
      London: Boosey & Hawkes, Limited, by arrangement with Edition Russe de Musique.
      E 8(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concerto en Mi b pour orchestre de chambre (Dumbarton Oaks 8-V-38)., 1938. (Box 41)
      C32(2[a]). This is the revised small score (plate 35383a) printed in Germany. L.M. has writtenrevised edition in the upper right hand corner of the cover.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Berceuses du chat (1916)., 1917. (Box 41)
      B13[1]. This is probably the earliest edition. Confusion arises as it appears that the first edition of the score was published by Chester and the first edition of the piano reduction by Ad Henn.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Berceuses du chat (1916)., 1925. (Box 41)
      Wien: Philharmonischer Verlag.
      B13[2]. DSL dates this plate no.W.Ph.V. 292/J.W.C 14a as 1917 Chester edition. This is a reprint of the 1917 score.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Suite no.1 for small orchestra (1925)., 1927. (Box 41)
      S30(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Sacre du Printemps] Danse sacrale from Le Sacre du Printemps (revised version 1943) for orchestra., 1945. (Box 41)
      S 6(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Trois pieces pour quatuor a cordes (1914)., 1922.; 2 copies. (Box 41)
      P35(3). The four-hand piano version is from 1914-15. The quartet is actually from 1918.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Trois pieces pour quatuor a cordes (1914)., 1922. (Box 41)
      P35(4). The four-hand piano version is from 1914-15. The quartet is actually from 1918.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Gorodetzky songs opus 6 no.2 Rosionka (Der Heilige Tau) (1908)., 1912 or 1913. (Box 41)
      Russian and German (ubersetzung von M.D. Calvocoressi).
      Soviet edition.(plate no.861).
      M11(). DSL makes reference to the German trans. but lists only the plate numbers of M11(1). Two copies in envelope: Library of Congress copy with cover--Biblioteque National copy, no cover.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Scherzo fantastique (1908) fur grosses orchester. (Box 41)
      S15(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concertino pour quatuor a cordes (1920)., 1923. (Box 41)
      C28(1). Signed by Gilbert Grau and L.M.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Symphonie Es-dur (1907)., 1914. (Box 41)
      Bad Godesberg: Rob. Forberg.
      S45(3).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Gorodetzky songs opus 6., 1920. (Box 41)
      Russian and German.
      Jurgenson Edition.
      M11(). DSL makes reference to the German translation but lists only the plate numbers of M11(1). Photocopy in envelope marked Stravinsky's own copy is this one, which he calls 'first edition'.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Gorodetzky songs opus 6 no.1 La Novice. Chanson de Printemps (Spring. The cloister) (1908)., 1912 or 1913. (Box 41)
      English and French translation by M.D. Calvocoressi.
      Moscow & Leipzig: P. Jurgenson and Rob. Forberg (plates 36199).
      M11(). DSL makes reference to the English and French translations but only lists the plate numbers of M11(1). Photocopy in envelope.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concerto en re (1931) pour violon et orchestre. (Box 41)
      C41(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Suite no.2 for chamber orchestra (1921)., 1925. (Box 41)
      S31(5).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Ragtime (1918) for 11 instruments., 1924. (Box 41)
      Wien: Philharmoniche Verlag.
      R 1(5). Reprint of 1921 J. & W. Chester edition.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Pulcinella Suite] Suite de Pulcinella (1920) pour petit orchestra d'apres J.B. Pergolesi., 1924. (Box 41)
      Edited by Albert Spalding, New York.
      P61(1). Some pencil clarifications of the instrumentation in L.M.'s hand.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Pulcinella suite (revised 1949 version). (Box 41)
      P63(1). Pencil notes in L.M.'s hand of differences between this and the 1924 edition.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Petrouchka (revised 1947 version) burlesque in four scenes., 1948. (Box 41)
      P16(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Baiser de la fee] Divertimento (nouvelle 1949 version) Suite du ballet: The fairy's kiss., 1950. (Box 41)
      B 9(1). Some pencil notes in L.M.'s hand, comparisons with the violin excerpts.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Epitaphium (1959) fur das grabmal des prinzen Max Egon zu Furstenberg. (Box 42)
      E 6(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Agon (1954-57) ballet for twelve dancers., 1957. (Box 42)
      A 4(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Septet (1953). (Box 42)
      S18(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Praeludium for jazz ensemble (1937, the string parts were added in June 1953)., 1968. (Box 42)
      P53(1). Confusion arises from the fact that the although the score indicates that the string parts were added in June 1953. Both versions have string parts.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Three songs from Shakespeare (1953) for mezzo soprano, flute, clarinet and viola., 1954. (Box 42)
      S26(2). Penciled serial analysis throughout.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--In memoriam Dylan Thomas (1954) for tenor voice, string quartet and four trombones. (Box 42)
      I 1(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Four songs for voice, flute, harp and guitar (1918, instr. 1953)., 1955. (Box 42)
      Phonetic Russian text by the composer. English translation by Robert Craft.
      S25(1). DSL dates this version 1954 contradicting published score.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Two poems [by Balmont] (1947) and three Japanese lyrics (1913) for high voice & piano., 1956. (Box 42)
      P49(2) & P51(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--J.S. Bach: Choral variationen uber das weinachtslied Vom Himmel hoch dakomm' ich her. (1956). (Box 42)
      Z 1(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Requiem canticles (1965-66) for contralto and bass soli, chorus and orchestra., 1967. (Box 42)
      London: Boosey & Hawkes Limited.
      R 9(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Movements (1958-59) for piano and orchestra., 1960. (Box 42)
      M14(1). Stamped for copyrighting purposes on front cover. Includes autographed analysis of 4th movement (2 sheets) by Ingolf Dahl. The opening is also analysed, apparently by L.M.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--A sermon, a narrative and a prayer (1960-61) cantata for alto and tenorsoli, speaker, chorus and orchestra., 1961. (Box 42)
      S20(2). Inserted are transcriptions of sketches by I.S. The score itself includes a serial analysis by L.M. in pencil throughout.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Abraham and Isaac (1963) a sacred ballad for baritone and chamber orchestra., 1965. (Box 42)
      A 1(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Sibelius, January Canzonetta opus 62a fur 8 instrumente gesetzt von Igor Stravinsky., 1964. (Box 42)
      Wiesbaden: Breitkopf & Hartel.
      Z14(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Elegy for J.F.K. (1964) mezzo soprano solo. (Box 42)
      Text by W.H. Auden.
      E 5(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Elegy for J.F.K. (1964) baritone solo. (Box 42)
      E 5(3).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Fanfare for a new theatre (1964)., 1968. (Box 42)
      Two trumpets.
      F 1(1). Inserted is a copy of the work in L.M.'s hand with serial analysis.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Introitus (1965) T.S. Eliot in memoriam for male chorus and chamber ensemble. (Box 42)
      I 4(). Large score is not listed in DSL.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Canon (1965) on a popular Russian tune for concert introduction or encore., 1973. (Box 42)
      C 1(1). Based on finale of L'Oiseau de feu.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Threni (1958) lamentiones Jeremiae prophetae. (Box 42)
      T 7(1). Includes many pencil notations and inserts, apparently L.M.'s transcription of Stravinsky's sketches.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Baiser de la fee] The fairy's kiss (1928) ballet in four scenes., 1978. (Box 42)
      Arranged for piano by K. Titarenko.
      Moscow: State Publishers Music.
      B 6(). Not listed in DSL.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Monumentum (1960) pro Gesualdo di Venosa ad CD annum. Three madrigals composed for instruments by Igor Stravinsky. (Box 42)
      M12(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Double canon (1959) Raoul Dufy in memoriam for string quartet., 1960. (Box 42)
      D 4(1). Penciled serial analysis in L.M.'s hand.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Gesualdo di Venosa, Carlo. Tres sacrae cantiones completed by Igor Stravinsky (1957)., 1960. (Box 42)
      Z 8(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Anthem (1962) The dove descending breaks the air for chorus a cappella. (Box 42)
      D 5(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--A sermon, a narrative and a prayer (1961) cantata for alto and tenor soli, speaker, chorus and orchestra. (Box 42)
      S21(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Stravinsky: The short piano pieces., 1977. (Box 42)
      Edited by Soulima Stravinsky.
      ZZ 1(). Not listed in DSL.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Septet (1953). (Box 42)
      S17(). In L.M.'s hand, serial analysis in multi-colored pencil.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Septet (1953). (Box 42)
      S17(). Not listed in DSL. Plate numbers identical (17447) to those listed for Hawkes pocket score.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Canticum sacrum (1955) ad honorem sancti Marci nominis for tenor and baritone soli, chorus and orchestra., 1956. (Box 42)
      C 5(2). Penciled serial analysis of second movement surge, aquilo.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Le Sacre du Printemps (The rite of spring) (1913) pictures of pagan Russia in two parts., 1921[sic].; 37 × 27.3cm. in size. (Box 43)
      New York: Boosey & Hawkes, Incorporated, printed by arrangement with Edition Russe de Musique.
      S 1(3). Includes errata sheet. This is a reprint of the 1929 revision plate no.B. & H. 16333. Pencil comparisons to R.M.V. 197 (1921!) and to original B. & H. Manuscript throughout.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Ave Maria (1934) pour chante mixte a capella. (Box 43)
      Text in Slavonic with transliteration.
      Berlin: Editions Russe de Musique.
      A 8(1). Includes a copy of this same edition in L.M.'s hand.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Jeu de cartes (1936)., 1937. (Box 43)
      C12(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concerto en Mi b pour orchestre de chambre (Dumbarton Oaks 8-V-38)., 1938. (Box 43)
      Reduction pour 2 pianos a 4 mains par l'auteur.
      Mainz: B. Scott's Sohne.
      C33(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Persephone (1934)., 1979. (Box 43)
      Melodrame en trois parties d'Andre Gide.
      Moscow: Editions Musique.
      P11(). Not listed in DSL, this score is a reproduction of P11(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Capriccio (1929)., 1930.; Photocopy. (Box 43)
      C 7(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Danses concertantes (1942)., 1944. (Box 43)
      Concert arrangement for two pianos by Ingolf Dahl.
      D 2(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Circus polka (1942)., 1948. (Box 43)
      C25(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Circus polka (1942)., 1943. (Box 43)
      Arranged for two pianos four hands by Victor Babin.
      C26(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Ave Maria (1949). (Box 43)
      Text in Latin.
      A 9(1). Two copies.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Circus polka [1942]. (Box 43)
      C23(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Mavra (1922)., 1947.; A photostatic reproduction from hand copied transparencies. (Box 43)
      Transcription for 2 pianos by Soulima Stravinsky.
      New York: Boosey and Hawkes, Incorporated, by arrangement with Edition Russe de Musique.
      M 4[a](M), apparently unpublished material.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--The rake's progress (1951) an opera in 3 acts. (Box 44)
      A fable by W.H. Auden and Chester Kallman. Deutsche ubersetzung von Fritz Schroder.
      R 5(1). Insert front cover errata list.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--The rake's progress (1951). (Box 44)
      A fable by W.H. Auden and Chester Kallman [English only].
      R 4(2). Insert before p.1: vol.1 errata list.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Le Rossignol (1914) conte lyrique en trois actes de I. Strawinsky et S. Mitousoff d'apres Anderson. (Box 44)
      Traduction francais de M.D. Calvocoressi.
      London: Boosey & Hawkes, Limited by arrangement with Edition Russe de Musique.
      R15(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Octet (1923 revised 1952) for wind instruments. (Box 45)
      O 2(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Wolf, Hugo. Two sacred songs from the Spanische liederbuch instrumentation by Igor Stravinsky (May 1968)., 1969. (Box 45)
      Z18(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--The owl and the pussycat (1966) for voice and piano., 1967. (Box 45)
      Poem by Edward Lear.
      O42(1). Affixed to inside front cover, a New Yorker cartoon of a man alone on a desert island about to be visited by an owl and a pussycat in a small boat.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Requiem canticles (1966) for contralto and bass soli, chorus and orchestra., 1967. (Box 45)
      R10(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--An album of Igor Stravinsky masterpieces arranged by Frederick Block, Gregory Stone and others. (Box 45)
      New York: Edward B. Mark's Music Corporation.
      ZZ 2(). Not listed in DSL.
    - Stravinskii, I.--P'esy: Obrabotka dlia skripki i fortepiano., 1967. (Box 45)
      Moskva: Muzyka.
      ZZ 3(). Not listed in DSL.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Baiser de la fee] The fairy's kiss (1928). A ballet in four scenes., 1954.; 2 copies. (Box 45)
      B 6(1). The copy with L.M.'s signature in the upper right corner of the cover includes occasional pencil and ink references to works of Tchaikovsky and Stravinsky.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Octet (1922) for wind instruments., 1926. (Box 45)
      O 3(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Abraham and Isaac (1962-63) a sacred ballad for baritone and chamber orchestra., 1965. (Box 45)
      A 2(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Babel (1944) cantata from the book of Moses I, capital II, verse 1-9 formale chorus and orchestra, with narrator (male)., 1952. (Box 45)
      B 2(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Le Rossignol (1914), conte lyrique en trois actes de I. Stravinsky et S. Mitousoff d'apres Andersen., 1961. (Box 45)
      French, English, German.
      R15(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Scherzo a la russe (1944) for orchestra., 1945. (Box 45)
      S14(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Sonata for two pianos (1943-44)., 1945. (Box 45)
      S24(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Abraham and Isaac (1963), a sacred ballad for baritone and chamber orchestra., 1965. (Box 45)
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Cantata (1952) for soprano, tenor, female chorus and a small instrumental ensemble. (Box 45)
      C 4(2). DSL's C 4(1) is listed as a Schott publication of this work, dated 1937, twelve years before its composition. Inserted are program notes from the premiere, 11 November 1952.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--The flood (1961-62) a musical play., 1963. (Box 45)
      F 8(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Mavra (1922), opera in one act after Pushkin by Boris Kochno., 1956. (Box 45)
      English, French and German.
      M 4(3).
    - [Stravinsky, Igor]--Four Russian peasant songs (1916)., 1932. (Box 46)
      R19(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[L']Histoire du soldat (1918)., 1924. (Box 46)
      Texte de C.F. Ramuz. English version by Rosa Newmarch. Freie nachdictung von Hans Reinhardt.
      H 3(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--l'Histoire du soldat, Valse (1918)., 1922. (Box 46)
      H 7(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--L'Histoire du soldat (1919) for violin, clarinet and piano., 196-[?]. (Box 46)
      H 5(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Sacre du Printemps] The rite of spring (1913)., 1975. (Box 46)
      New York: Lyra Music Company.
      S 2(). Not listed in DSL.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Four Russian peasant songs (new version, 1954) for equal voices with four horns., 1958. (Box 46)
      R20(1). Includes some penciled comparisons to other editions.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Four Russian peasant songs (1916)., 1950. (Box 46)
      New York: Marks Music Corporation by arrangement with J. & W. Chester, Limited.
      R19(3). Identical with Chester ed. 9732, and pno red for rehearsal.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Quatre etudes pour orchestre] Madrid from four studies for orchestra., 1951. (Box 46)
      E11(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--L'Oiseau de feu (1910) conte danse en 2 tableaux., n.d. (Box 46)
      New York: Broude Brothers.
      O 8(2). Affixed to inside front cover is a postcard-photo of Karsavina as firebird, 1910.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Sacre du Printemps] The rite of spring (1913)., 1973. (Box 46)
      Moscow: Le Compositeur Sovietique.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Sacre du Printemps] The rite of spring (1913) pictures of pagan Russia., n.d. (Box 46)
      S 1(). Reproduction of 1921 Edition Russe de Musique (1929 revision), S 1(1). Includes errata list by Dr. Glenn Block, University of Missouri.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[Le Sacre du Printemps] The rite of spring (1913) ballet for orchestra by Igor Stravinsky and Nicolas Roerich., 1926. (Box 46)
      S 3(). DSL lists S 3(1) as a 1913 Edition Russe de Musique (plate no.RMV 196). This is plate B. & H. 17271. Occasional pencil and ink comparisons with other editions.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Le Sacre du Printemps, Tourney of rival tribes for piano solo., 1941. (Box 46)
      New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corporation.
      S 7(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Four Russian peasant songs (1916)., 1973. (Box 46)
      Soviet publication.
      R19(). Not listed in DSL.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Duo concertant (1932) pour violon et piano., 1938. (Box 47)
      D 7(2).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Ode (1943) tryptychon fur orchester., 1968. (Box 47)
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Renard (1917[sic]) a burlesque for the stage to be sung and acted based on popular Russian folk tales., 1956 (English translation--copyright date). (Box 47)
      French text by C.F. Ramuz. English text by Rollo H. Myers.
      R 8(3?) Plate J.W.C. 9716. Penciled Russian transliteration throughout, In L.M.'s hand: (older edition, some errors in it) Transliteration of Russian text.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Le Rossignol (1914) conte lyrique en trois actes de I. Stravinsky et S. Mitousoff d'apres Andersen., 1962. (Box 47)
      Traduction francaise de M.D. Calvocoressi. English translation by Robert Craft. Deutscheubertragung von A. Elukhen und B. Feiwel.
      London: Boosey & Hawkes by arrangement with Edition Russe de Musique.
      R14(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concertino (1920)., 1923. (Box 47)
      Revised and edited by Julia A. Burt.
      C29(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concertino pour quatuor a cordes (1920)., 1925.; Two copies. (Box 47)
      C31(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Les Noces (1917) scenes choreographiques, russes avec chant et musique composees., 1922. (Box 47)
      Version francaise de C.F. Ramuz.
      N 2(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Pulcinella (1920) ballet in one act after Giambattista Pergolesi. (Box 47)
      J. & W. Chester, Limited.
      P60(1). Some rehearsal numbers added in red pencil.
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concerto en re (1931) pour violon et orchestre. (Box 47)
      Violin part in collaboration with Samuel Dushkin.
      C42(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Concerto (1935) per due pianoforte soli., 1936. (Box 47)
      C38(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--Symphony of psalms (1930, rev. 1948) for mixed chorus and orchestra. (Box 47)
      S38(1).
    - Stravinsky, Igor--[L'Oiseau de feu] Scherzo tiree du ballet L'Oiseau de feu., 1933. (Box 49)
      Mainz: B. Schott's Sohne (from Forberg).